{
    "subject": "resource/Salah_Mansour",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathDate",
    "object": "1979-01-19",
    "human_readable": "Salah Mansour died on January 19th, 1979.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9015853404998779,
            "question": "When did Salah Mansour die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8105331659317017,
            "question": "What year was Salah Mansour's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8092209100723267,
            "question": "In what month did Salah Mansour die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7399710416793823,
            "question": "Who was Salah Mansour?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5472854971885681,
            "question": "Is January 19th, 1979 a known historical event?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5347429513931274,
            "question": "On what date did Salah Mansour pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4571497440338135,
            "question": "Is there anything else you know about January 19th, 1979?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44829973578453064,
            "question": "Were there any notable events associated with Salah Mansour's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41490593552589417,
            "question": "What field was Salah Mansour known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39572227001190186,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Salah Mansour?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Salah Mansour died on January 19th, 1979.",
            "html": "dbpedia_221_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field was Salah Mansour known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_221_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable events associated with Salah Mansour's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_221_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else you know about January 19th, 1979?",
            "html": "dbpedia_221_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_221_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_221_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_221_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_221_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_221_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_221_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_221_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_221_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_221_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_221_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThe documents provide clear information that Salah Mansour died on January 19, 1979. This directly supports the statement \"Salah Mansour died on January 19th, 1979.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}